[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many continents are owned by only one nation?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "2", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Victoria Falls are situated on the Zambezi River, on the border between which two countries?", "correct_answer": "Zambia and Zimbabwe", "incorrect_answers": ["Tanzania and Zaire", "Kenya and Tanzania", "Zambia and Zaire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Indonesian island was in the news in 2003 when the remains of an extinct variety of small hominids (popularly referred to as Hobbits), measuring about 3 feet in height, were found there?", "correct_answer": "Flores", "incorrect_answers": ["Sumatra", "New Guinea", "Timor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shaanxi earthquake is regarded as the deadliest recorded earthquake, killing approximately 830,000 people. It occurred on February 14, 1556 in this country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Thailand", "Japan", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city, known also as Anvil City, is situated  in Northwest Alaska.", "correct_answer": "Nome", "incorrect_answers": ["Stockton", "Palmer", "Barrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of a cell contains the chromosomes or genetic material?", "correct_answer": "Nucleus", "incorrect_answers": ["Endoplasmic Reticulum", "Cytoplasm", "Golgi Apparatus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apart from its culinary properties, sugar has many uses in science and manufacturing. It is used for all of the following, except one.", "correct_answer": "To increase ice creams freezing point", "incorrect_answers": ["To tan leather, printer inks and dyes.", "To harden asphalt.", "To help grow penicillin."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the deity whose statue Achilles beheaded in the film Troy?", "correct_answer": "Apollo", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphrodite", "Zeus", "Hercules"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these best describes the meaning of the word, seiche?", "correct_answer": "Standing wave in a body of water", "incorrect_answers": ["Alignment of three or more celestial bodies", "Horizontal mass of rock, intruded between older layers of sedimentary rock", "Change in the Earths magnetic field in and around the source of a tsunami"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pandas live in the mountains in the Sichuan, Shaanxi, and Gansu provinces in this country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Mongolia", "Thailand", "Korea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many stories does the Empire State Building have?", "correct_answer": "102", "incorrect_answers": ["100", "150", "109"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What  vitamin is found in high amounts in the bitter root of the turnip plant?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin E", "Vitamin B12", "Vitamin A"]}]